[{"answer": "Yes, I've been in bad shape.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 20, "question": "Have you ever been in bad shape your whole life?", "qSentId": 19}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Seth, I've never met you, have I?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "And do you understand why people like you and I never win the Emmy?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "I mean, it's -- I don't know if it's that specific, but I think it's -- I think the Emmys do tend to make safe choices.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "-- an Emmy to an atheist?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "It's possible.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Do you think the fact that you're politically outspoken plays a role in maybe not winning awards?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "And you don't?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "I mean, this -- your \"Family Guy\" has been on what, 11 years?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You don't want to wrap it up, do you?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I think at this point, yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "You'll do it as long as they'll let you, won't you?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I feel like if I knew, if I was in those little rooms or those big rooms --", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "What are you disappointed in?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Well, Bill, good a time as any to make this announcement.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Now why, of all the causes, not that we don't agree that that should have been done, but why that?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "Not in Beverly Hills, but I mean --", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Is there always locusts?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Well, when we do table reads for the shows, I -- it's a necessity, I have to jump around, you know, \"Hey, Quagmire, how's it going?\"", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "How do you do it when they're all talking together in the same scene?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Yes, you know, I mean, my generation has -- grew up with that and it's, like it or not, we all know it backwards and forwards.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "So that was your tribute to -- I remember when that played, that was this whole hour episode, right, because that was, for some reason, something that was very influential in your childhood, \"Star Wars,\" right?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I was actually more of a --", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "You can't have both?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I was about 2 years old, I think.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "How old were you when you made that?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "You did do that at 2?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Oh, 20, OK.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "I was, what, 20?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "I've maybe seen \"American Idol\" twice.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "What do you think of shows like \"American Idol,\" the singing and \"The Voice\" and all these singing contests that are on TV?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "I've never seen \"The Voice.\"", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "You've avoided it?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "I've mentioned it before.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "Does that count?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "It's tough to get --", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "What about procedural crime shows?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "You are that bear?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "I'm -- yes, I'm in the bear costume.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "You're in that bear costume?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I'd say, hey, it's \"You, Me and Dupree\" with fuzz.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "So if you were pitching it, and you had to do something meets something, what would it be?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "She plays --", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "Who does she play?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "The love interest of Mark Wahlberg.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "Of the bear?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "No, no, I do not.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "So you don't get the girl?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "It did?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "Well, at some point in the future you may.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "We're never going to see that?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Kind of the other problem.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Is it not?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "That, you know, there were a number of issues with -- the predominant issue was schedule, but you know, there was -- it was a challenge to -- in a world where there are so many animated fathers on television who can trace their cartoon lineage directly back to Fred Flintstone, where does Fred Flintstone fit in himself?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "You're bringing that back on FOX?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Right on regular TV?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Well, fans of the original will know more or less what to look for.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "So what is that -- what can people look forward to with that show?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely, yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "One of your heroes, right?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Academia.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "One of the very influential writer -- and the last guy to really bridge the gap between science and between academia and -- is that word, academia?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "The problem is that if I tell you, hey, there's a monster living under my bed, you would say, well, that sounds ridiculous.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 471, "question": "-- kind of really one or the other, right?", "qSentId": 470}, {"answer": "RMSTRONG: I'm a -- yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Are you an exercise nut?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "And -- have you ever been in bad shape in your whole life?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, Prop 29 is a -- is a price increase on a pack of cigarettes in the state of California.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What is it asking for?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, it's certainly safe to say that the gloves are off here.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "Yes, at the time, only five of them.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "And I guess it's a little dated there, Lance, because at that point, you'd only won the Tour de France five times and you've actually won it seven, didn't you?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "RMSTRONG: No, I mean I think there's certainly a mental part of this.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "Is it a mental thing?", "qSentId": 610}, {"answer": "It depends how you describe pain.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Is it not very just painful at a certain point?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "You know, I -- I -- I saw the former president about a year ago.", "docId": "120601pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Do you see him when you're in Texas?", "qSentId": 654}]